{"response_code":0,"results":[{"category":"Geography","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"Which of the following operator is used for the Assignment Operator?","correct_answer":"=","incorrect_answers":["!","==","+"]},{"category":"Geography","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"What is the symbol pair used to write a new line within a string values?","correct_answer":"\n","incorrect_answers":["\m","\*","\br"]},{"category":"Geography","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"What is the symbol used for the INCREMENT operator in JS?","correct_answer":"++","incorrect_answers":["+","=","=="]},{"category":"Geography","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"Conditions return values of which data type?","correct_answer":"boolean","incorrect_answers":["Integer","floating-point","string"]},{"category":"Geography","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"file extension for external JS files","correct_answer":".js","incorrect_answers":[".javascript",".jscript",".script"]},{"category":"Geography","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"built in object in JS that allows a script to perform mathematical task","correct_answer":"Math Object","incorrect_answers":["Arithmetic","Operation Object","Mathematics Object"]},{"category":"Geography","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"used to write comments","correct_answer":"//","incorrect_answers":["=","++","--"]},{"category":"Geography","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"A string;","correct_answer":"can contain letters, numbers, spaces, and symbols.","incorrect_answers":["Expresses a true false statement","takes in an input, does something with it, and then returns an output.","Runs a boolean (true/false) statement based on data entered"]},{"category":"Geography","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"What surrounds a string?","correct_answer":"Quotations","incorrect_answers":["Curly Brackets","Parenthesis","Square Brackets"]},{"category":"Geography","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"To display writing on the screen you must include this direction;","correct_answer":"document.write( )","incorrect_answers":["documentWrite","Document Write","document.write"]}]}
